

# CONTACT

- +91 9074212751
- muhammeduvais907@gmail.com
- kootilangadi, Malappuram 676506, Kerala, India

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2019 - 2021

Diploma Computer
Engineering

### 2017 - 2018

 PLUS TWO (Computee Science)

#### 2005 - 2016

 SSLC (Secondary Education)-Kerala state board

# PHYSICAL STATUS

• Hearing Impaired Disability: 71%

# **SKILLS**

- Front-end Development
- Back-end Development
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Bootstrap
- Django
- Python
- Git/Github

# LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam

# **MUHAMMED UVAIS OK**

# PYTHON FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

# **PROFILE**

As a Python full-stack developer, I have extensive experience developing and deploying full-stack web applications using Python frameworks such as Django. 1 have strong skills in front-end development and back-end development technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

### **EXPERIENCE**

GEDEXO DESIGN AND TECHNOLOGY LLP

python full-stsck web developer

2023 - PRESENT

- Developed and designed cone sites for clients
- Collaborated with clients and team members to ensure project goals were met
- Provided website maintenance and support to clients

### OXDUTECH

python full-stsck web developer

2023 - 2024

- website developer and website design
- Developed and designed e-commerce websites
- Educational institutions

### **HOBBIES**

- · Playing Football
- chess

### **AWARDS**

• Running competition, Painting, Quiz competition

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Selected at State level in Long Jump.
- · Has been selected for the district in Food ball

### **OBJECTIVE**

 To take the challenging and responsive assignment in a reputed and well organised company where I can prove my excellence abilities, skill and my work will be recognized and justified

# **PROJECTS**

- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/odadoz-e-commerce.git
- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/danbury.git
- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/mobile-shopil.git